[
    {
      "question": "The .container class provides a full width container, spanning the entire width of the screen",
      "option": [
        "False",
        "True"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class provides a responsive fixed width container?",
      "option": [
        ".container-fixed",
        ".container-responsive",
        ".container",
        ".container-fluid"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which contextual class is used to create an orange text color?",
      "option": [
        ".txt-warning",
        ".text-warning",
        ".bg-warning",
        ".txt-orange"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "The Bootstrap grid system is based on how many columns?",
      "option": [
        "12",
        "9",
        "3",
        "6"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class adds zebra-stripes to a table?",
      "option": [
        ".table-zebra",
        ".table-bordered",
        ".table-striped",
        ".even and .odd"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class shapes an image to a circle?",
      "option": [
        ".img-round",
        ".img-rounded",
        ".img-circle",
        ".rounded-circle"
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class is used to create a big box for calling extra attention?",
      "option": [
        ".container",
        ".jumbotron",
        ".bigbox",
        "There is no such class"
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class is used to create a button group?",
      "option": [
        ".group-btn",
        ".btn-group",
        ".group-button",
        ".button-group"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which button class is used to create a large button?",
      "option": [
        ".btn-l",
        ".btn-lg",
        ".btn-large",
        ".btn-l2"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class is used to create a badge?",
      "option": [
        ".badge-item",
        ".badge-label",
        ".label-badge",
        ".badge"
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class is used to create a loader?",
      "option": [
        ".spinner-loader",
        ".spinner-border",
        ".loader",
        ".spinner"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class is used to create a basic pagination?",
      "option": [
        ".pagination",
        ".page",
        ".pages",
        ".navigation"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class is used to create a basic list group?",
      "option": [
        ".grouped-list",
        ".list-group",
        ".group-list"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class adds a heading to a card?",
      "option": [
        ".card-footer",
        ".card-head",
        ".card-header",
        ".card-heading"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class indicates a dropdown menu?",
      "option": [
        ".dropdown-list",
        ".dropdown",
        ".select"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class is used to create a vertical navigation bar?",
      "option": [
        ".navbar",
        ".navbar navbar-vertical",
        ".navbar-vertical",
        ".navbar-inverse"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which component is used to cycle through elements, like a slideshow?",
      "option": [
        "Carousel",
        "Slideshow",
        "Scrollspy",
        "Orbit"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which contextual class indicates a succesful or positive action?",
      "option": [
        ".bg-info",
        ".bg-warning",
        ".bg-primary",
        ".bg-success"
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which contextual class indicates a dangerous or potentially negative action?",
      "option": [
        ".bg-dark",
        ".bg-primary",
        ".bg-info",
        ".bg-danger"
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class indicates uppercased text?",
      "option": [
        ".text-uppercase",
        ".ucase",
        ".uppercase",
        ".text-capitalize"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which attribute is used to create a tooltip?",
      "option": [
        "data-bs-toggle=\"modal\"",
        "data-bs-toggle=\"tooltip\"",
        "data-bs-toggle=\"collapse\"",
        "data-bs-toggle=\"popup\""
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "A standard navigation tab is created with:",
      "option": [
        "<ul class=\"nav nav-navbar\">",
        "<ul class=\"nav nav-tabs\">",
        "<ul class=\"nav tabs\">",
        "<ul class=\"navigation-tabs\">"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "A standard navigation bar is created with:",
      "option": [
        "<nav class=\"nav navbar\">",
        "<nav class=\"navigationbar navbar-default\">",
        "<nav class=\"navbar navbar-expand-sm\">",
        "<nav class=\"navbar navbar-default\">"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class is used to style a close icon?",
      "option": [
        ".btn-x",
        ".x",
        ".close-icon",
        ".btn-close"
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which class can be used to float an element to the right of the page?",
      "option": [
        ".float-right",
        ".float-r",
        ".float-end",
        ".float-start"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    }
  ]